[
  {
    "question": "What term describes government actions and regulations aimed at protecting the environment?",
    "answer": "Environmental policy",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6e" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for agreements between nations to address global environmental issues?",
    "answer": "International treaties",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6e" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes rules and regulations set by a government to limit pollution?",
    "answer": "Environmental regulations",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6e" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the process of using economic incentives to encourage environmental protection?",
    "answer": "Market-based instruments",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6e" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the practice of assigning a monetary value to environmental goods and services?",
    "answer": "Environmental valuation",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6e" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the study of the interactions between organisms and their environment?",
    "answer": "Ecology",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for the number of different species in a particular habitat or ecosystem?",
    "answer": "Biodiversity",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes a group of organisms of the same species living in the same area?",
    "answer": "Population",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the relationship between two species where one benefits and the other is unaffected?",
    "answer": "Commensalism",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes a group of different populations living and interacting with each other in an area?",
    "answer": "Community",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd6f" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the study of preserving biodiversity and protecting natural habitats?",
    "answer": "Conservation biology",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd70" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the prevention of habitat destruction and the protection of endangered species?",
    "answer": "Habitat conservation",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd70" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes efforts to restore ecosystems to their original state?",
    "answer": "Ecological restoration",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd70" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the protection and management of forests for environmental sustainability?",
    "answer": "Forest conservation",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd70" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the process of protecting marine ecosystems and species?",
    "answer": "Marine conservation",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd70" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes energy derived from natural sources that are constantly replenished?",
    "answer": "Renewable energy",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd71" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes the conversion of sunlight into electricity?",
    "answer": "Solar power",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd71" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes energy generated from moving water, such as rivers or tides?",
    "answer": "Hydropower",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd71" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes energy produced from organic materials, such as plants and waste?",
    "answer": "Biomass energy",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd71" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  },
  {
    "question": "What term describes energy generated from the heat stored in the Earth's crust?",
    "answer": "Geothermal energy",
    "category": { "$oid": "6619a4a3e77c7a8772fe74e1" },
    "subcategory": { "$oid": "6632205ff9c6588c4fbebd71" },
    "__v": { "$numberInt": "0" }
  }
]
